<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sunday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/sunday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sunday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/sunday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The stone rejected by the builders</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/12042020-easter-sunday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/12042020-easter-sunday/</guid>
      <description>“The stone that the builders rejected has become the chief cornerstone. This is the LORD’s doing; it is wonderful in our eyes.”
In these powerful words of Psalm 118, the earliest disciples of Jesus found the key to understanding the mystery of Christ Crucified and the still greater mystery of Christ Risen.
As the world continues to battle our most recent pandemic, we remember the many faces of Christ Crucified throughout the ages, from those thrown away to die in the streets, to those herded into extermination camps; from those abused by family, friends or clergy, to those whose dreams and ambitions have utterly failed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Crucify Him”: The Place of God amidst Evil</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/05042020-sun6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/05042020-sun6/</guid>
      <description>Passion Sunday, Year A, 2020Isaiah 50:4-7Philippians 2:6-11Matthew 26:14—27:66Today we enter into Holy Week. The week is made holy by its celebration of Jesus&amp;rsquo; gift of himself to us and for us. Wednesday, we remember his betrayal. Thursday is a celebration of the gift of the Eucharist and a reflection on the example of service Jesus gives to us. Friday is &amp;ldquo;Good&amp;rdquo; because we truly remember how much he loved us - even with his death on the cross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Triumph of Grace, because “Jesus Wept”</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/29032020-sun5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/29032020-sun5/</guid>
      <description>Fifth Sunday of Lent Year A 2020Ezekiel 37:12-14;Psalms 130: 1-2,3-4,5-7a. 7 6,-8 Romans 8:8-11; John 11:1-45 Quite often, we fail to tap into the knowledge of our faith to help us to weather the storms of temptations and trials. For example, how often do we remember the meaning of grace/hope which we learnt in our Catechism classes – “Grace is the supernatural gift of God which makes us believe that God will do everything for our justification and salvation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am the light of the world</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/22032020-sun4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/22032020-sun4/</guid>
      <description>Fourth Sunday of Lent Year A 2020.Samuel 16:1b.6-7.10-13a.Psalm 23:1-3a.3h-4.5.Ephesians 5:8-14.John 9:1-41.The weather is becoming hotter and with the longer hours of daylight than night, the flowers begin to spring, trees budding and green foilage appear. The warmth of the light from the sun is rejuvenating, not only for nature but also for our personal wellbeing.
But the light of the sun is not the only light that is available to make our days more enjoyable, for we can also choose to walk in the light of the Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A spring of water welling up to eternal life</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/15032020-sun3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/15032020-sun3/</guid>
      <description>Third Sunday of Lent Year A 2020Exodus 17:3-7Psalms 95:1-2, 6-7, 8-9Romans 5:1-2, 5-8John 4:5-42We talk about Lent as a time of invitation from God. What does God want to give us this Lent?
We begin by looking at the story of a woman who sees how she can change her life; how she can change the patterns of her life. She leaves behind her fears and her embarrassment and begins a new life – she sees that God has an invitation for her and she says, Yes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Listening Prayer: A Journey into the Cloud!</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/08032020-sun2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/08032020-sun2/</guid>
      <description>Sunday of the Second Week of Lent Year A 2020Psalms 33:4-5, 18-19, 20, 222 Timothy 1:8B-10Matthew 17:1-9Nigerian Christianity calls it Shekinah glory but the Jews only call it Shekinah, that is the presence of God as Cloud. In the Old Testament tradition, where God led his enslaved children from Egypt to the Promised Land, the pillar of Cloud showed God’s presence while he travelled with his people — a traveling God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning our Temptations into Strengths</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/01032020-sun1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/01032020-sun1/</guid>
      <description>Sunday of the First Week of Lent, Year A, 2020Genesis 2:7-9; 3:1-7Psalm 51: 3-4, 5-6, 12-13, 14, 17Romans 5:12-19Matthew 4:1-11When I listen to homilies these days, they emphasis that the damnation of sinners tromps the salvation of sinners; but Jesus didn’t come to condemn sinners, he came to save sinners. When “prosperity gospel” is not preached, on a Sunday, then “end times prediction” is the next viable topic of interest among evangelists and prophets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>