<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Saturday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/saturday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Saturday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/saturday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the Easter Vigil</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/11042020-holy-saturday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/11042020-holy-saturday/</guid>
      <description>On Good Friday, there was no Eucharist - simply a communion service, with the Body of Christ from the Holy Thursday Eucharist.
On Holy Saturday, there is no liturgy at all. The liturgy this evening is the vigil - the preparation for and entry into the celebration of Our Lord&amp;rsquo;s Resurrection. It is an Easter Sunday liturgy. On Holy Saturday we enter into the mystery. Today we contemplate Jesus, there in the tomb, dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is better for one man to die for the people</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/04042020-sat5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/04042020-sat5/</guid>
      <description>Saturday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Ezekiel 37:21-28Jeremiah 31:10, 11-12ABCD, 13John 11:45-56In today’s gospel and we are reminded of what is coming. We rejoice in the great love of Jesus for us. Our Lenten journey has brought us here.
It is as though we, too, are gathering in Jerusalem to celebrate our Passover week.
We are ready to enter into the Passion drama, and to celebrate the Paschal Mystery, with mind and heart renewed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Christ will not come from Galilee</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/28032020-sat4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/28032020-sat4/</guid>
      <description>Saturday of the Fourth Week of Lent Year A 2020Jeremiah 11:18-20Psalms 7:2-3, 9bc-10, 11-12John 7:40-53Today&amp;rsquo;s readings are both about recognizing God and responding appropriately to God.
In the preceding passages in Jeremiah, God told Jeremiah to remind the people that they have ignored God&amp;rsquo;s covenant and rules. They ignore God and they ignore God&amp;rsquo;s messenger and worship false gods. In today&amp;rsquo;s reading they want to eliminate Jeremiah who was reminder to them of their evil ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>God, be merciful to me a sinner</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/21032020-sat3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/21032020-sat3/</guid>
      <description>Saturday of the Third Week of Lent Year A 2020*Hosea 6:1-6.Psalm 51:3-4.18-19.20-21ab.Luke 18:9-14.In both readings today, there is a contrast between what God wants and what people bring him.
In the first reading, the people bring sacrifices and holocausts to God in the Temple, but in response God, speaking through the prophet Hosea, says, ‘what I want is love, not sacrifice; knowledge of God, not holocausts’. God wants the love of his people, a love that finds expression in the love of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your brother was dead and has come to life</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/14032020-sat2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/14032020-sat2/</guid>
      <description>Saturday of the Second Week of Lent Year A 2020Micah 7:14-15, 18-20Psalms 103:1-2, 3-4, 9-10, 11-12Luke 15:1-3, 11-32There are few readings of the scriptures that are more frequently alluded to or commented on than the story of the “Prodigal Son”. Rightly understood we realize the story focuses on the prodigality of God and God’s mercy more than it focuses on the immature and self-driven decisions of the sinner (child) in the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn our hearts to you, Eternal Father</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/07032020-sat1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/07032020-sat1/</guid>
      <description>Saturday of the First Week of Lent Year A 2020Deuteronomy 26:16-19Psalms 119:1-2, 4-5, 7-8Matthew 5:43-48When I got to the end of the Gospel reading for today, I sighed. A big sigh. Jesus doesn’t make it easy. Be perfect. Love your enemies.
 In a time of polarizing partisanship with name-calling and filter bubbles, I tend to wrap myself in indignation and superiority over those I consider wrong and against what I stand for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinners called to a New Existence with God</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/29022020-sat0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/29022020-sat0/</guid>
      <description>Saturday after Ash Wednesday Year A 2020Isaiah 58:9-14Luke 5:27-32In the first reading, what the Lord is telling His people is certainly something that is not beyond their reach or impossible to achieve. It is the very basics of being human – doing away with the yoke, the clenched fist, the wicked word, giving bread to the hungry, relief to the oppressed. In return, they will be like a watered garden, a spring of water, called “Breach-mender” and “Restorer of ruined houses”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>