<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Monday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/monday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Monday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/monday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>She had to keep this scent for the day of my burial</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/06042020-mon6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/06042020-mon6/</guid>
      <description>Monday of Holy Week Year A 2020Isaiah 42:1-7Psalms 27:1, 2, 3, 13-14John 12:1-11One of the most significant and powerful gifts that one person can share with another is the gift of compassion.
Compassion rises from deep within and becomes an almost unstoppable movement toward someone in response to their pain. We respond with love in a gesture of care and a meaningful, sacred encounter emerges.
In our gospel story today, Mary, Martha and Lazarus, who are friends of Jesus, host a dinner for him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neither do I condemn you</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/30032020-mon5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/30032020-mon5/</guid>
      <description>Monday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Daniel 13:1-9, 15-17, 19-30, 33-62Psalms 23:1-3a, 3b-4, 5, 6John 8:1-11Today’s Gospel presents the story of the woman caught in adultery, which is one of the clearest demonstrations of what can called the scapegoat mechanism.
This is another one of John’s gospel demonstrating the mercy of God. God is not interested in our past but what the future will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miracles are more than magic</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/23032020-mon4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/23032020-mon4/</guid>
      <description>Monday of the Fourth Week of Lent Year A 2020Isaiah 65:17-21Psalms 30:2 and 4, 5-6, 11-12a, and 13bJohn 4:43-54In today’s first reading, the prophet Isaiah is preaching to a people who have been recently traumatized by the experience of exile. They had returned home to a land and a city that was in ruins. At such a moment, the prophet speaks a message of hope from the Lord, ‘I create new heavens and a new earth, and the past will not be remembered… I now create Jerusalem “Joy” and her people “Gladness”’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Like Elijah and Elisha, Jesus was sent not only to the Jews</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/16032020-mon3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/16032020-mon3/</guid>
      <description>Monday of the Third Week of Lent Year A 20202 Kings 5:1-15abPsalms 42:2, 3, 43:3,4 Luke 4:24-30Today&amp;rsquo;s Lenten readings seem to be about letting God heal us.
Naaman hears there is a prophet in this foreign land who could cure his skin disease. The trouble is, he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like what Elisha suggests for his healing. His logic goes: The rivers of my home in Damascus, Syria, would have been just fine to wash in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord, do not deal with us according to our sins</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/09032020-mon2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/09032020-mon2/</guid>
      <description>Monday of the Second Week of Lent Year A 2020Daniel 94B-10Psalms 798, 9, 11 and 13Luke 636-38We live in such an individualistic society. We may be part of a church, club, or family but it is easy for many to disown the group when things are not as they should be.
The first reading from the Book of Daniel is one of the great acts of sorrow to God for sin in the Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How should I welcome another?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/02032020-mon1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/02032020-mon1/</guid>
      <description>Monday of the First Week of Lent Year A 2020Leviticus 19: 1-2, 11-18Psalm 19: 8- 10, 15Matthew 25:31-46It’s Lent again. What will I give up versus what will I do?
Only yesterday, lost in my musings, I almost walked into a woman in tattered clothing on the street She is startled and says, &amp;ldquo;I am sorry&amp;rdquo;. I smile and say, “I’m sorry, too.” I walk on. I don’t see her again, but I can’t get her off my mind because in our world today, ordinarily nobody will want to say sorry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>