<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/friday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/friday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Into your hands I commend my spirit</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/10042020-good-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/10042020-good-friday/</guid>
      <description>Good Friday of the Lord&#39;s Passion Year A 2020Isaiah 52:13--53:12Psalms 31:2, 6, 12-13, 15-16, 17, 25Hebrews 4:14-16; 5:7-9John 18:1--19:42What started as like jokes worldwide have made the world to become a very strange place as we respond to COVID-19.
We never knew it will look like this as we arrive at Good Friday on April 10, 2020. At this point, in most places around the world, Triduum in Catholic churches will look much different than it usually does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They wanted to stone Jesus, but he eluded them</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/03042020-fri5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/03042020-fri5/</guid>
      <description>Friday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Jeremiah 20:10-13Psalms 18:2-3SA, 3BC-4, 5-6, 7John 10:31-42In the current culture few people reach the age of 21 years without experiencing some of the anxiety and terror that the first reading expresses today. It is as if everywhere one looks, someone seems to have it in for others – is prepared to make life miserable for no just cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They would have arrested him but his time had not yet come</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/27032020-fri4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/27032020-fri4/</guid>
      <description>Friday of the Fourth Week of Lent Year 2020Wisdom 2:1a, 12-22Psalms 34:17-1, 19-20, 21 and 23John 7:1-2, 10, 25-30The Book of Wisdom from which our first reading came was written less than one hundred years before the coming of Jesus. It is probably closer to the time of Jesus than any other book of the Old Testament.
In our reading, the author places a little speech on the lips of those who were hostile to people of faith, those who took their Jewish faith seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lord our God is one Lord, and you shall love the Lord your God</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/20032020-fri3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/20032020-fri3/</guid>
      <description>Friday of the Third Week of Lent Year A 2020Hosea 14:1-9.Psalm 81:6c-8a.8bc-9.10-11ab.14 &amp;amp; 17.Mark 12:28b-34.Among the many hopeful texts of the various prophetic books, today’s first reading from the prophet Hosea is one of the most beautiful and poignant.
We hear in the text the voice of a loving God, who has entered a covenant relationship with chosen humans that is analogous to the commitment of spouses to one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They will respect my Son</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/13032020-fri2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/13032020-fri2/</guid>
      <description>Friday of the Second Week of Lent Year A 2020Genesis 37:3-4, 12-13a, 17b-28a Psalms 105:16-17, 18-19, 20-21 Matthew 21:33-43, 45-46Believe it or not, today’s readings present not just two stories that mirror each other—the story of Joseph rejected by his brothers (who will emerge to becomes their saviour) and the story of Jesus rejected by the leaders of his day (only to become the saviour of his people) — but four stories that all have this same theme: The rejected one becomes the saviour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live life above average with spirit of consistency</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/06032020-fri1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/06032020-fri1/</guid>
      <description>Friday of the first week in Lent Year A 2020Ezekiel 18:21-28Psalm 130:1-8Matthew 5:20-26No one likes to be told what to do. In general, we dislike laws and regulations. Rules can vary from being annoying to stifling to burdensome. As a result, we try to find ways to avoid following the rules and look for short cut. We ask ourselves how we can get away with doing the minimum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting for the Kingdom of God</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/28022020-fri0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/28022020-fri0/</guid>
      <description>Friday after Ash Wednesday Year A 2020Isaiah 58: 1 - 9Matthew 9: 14 - 15Fasting as a form of penance is often highlighted during the Lenten Season. On Ash Wednesday, we talked about fasting and doing penance. Today’s reading also talked about fasting.
In the first reading prophet Isaiah pointed out to the people that they abused and misused the religious meaning of fasting. They practised fasting but their lives did not reflect the act of doing penance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>