<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thursday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/thursday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thursday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/thursday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Love one another</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/09042020-holy-thursday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/09042020-holy-thursday/</guid>
      <description>Holy Thursday Evening Mass of the Lord’s Supper Year A 2020Exodus 12:1-8, 11-14Psalm 116:12-13, 15-16bc, 17-181 Corinthians 11:23-26John 13:1-15This evening we begin the holy days of the Paschal Triduum, ending Lent and walking with Jesus to his death and resurrection. These days are about Jesus. But, we too, in the company of Jesus, have our part in the story. Why? Because, we live daily the Paschal Mystery of Life, Death and Resurrection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your father Abraham saw my Day and was glad</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/02042020-thur5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/02042020-thur5/</guid>
      <description>Thursday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Genesis 17:3-9Psalms 105:4-5, 6-7, 8-9John 8:51-59In last Monday’s gospel reading, the religious leaders were ready to stone a woman whom they had brought to Jesus. In this morning’s gospel reading, the same group pick up stones in order to stone Jesus. They wanted to stone the woman because she had sinned by committing adultery; they wanted to stone Jesus because of the claims that he was making for himself, such as his claim that he existed before Abraham was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You placed your hopes on Moses, but Moses will be your accuser</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/26032020-thur4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/26032020-thur4/</guid>
      <description>Thursday of the Fourth Week of Lent Year A 2020Exodus 32:7-14Psalms 106:19-20, 21-22, 23John 5:31-47Exodus 32: 7-14 The Golden Calf
Then the LORD said to Moses: Go down at once because your people, whom you brought out of the land of Egypt, have acted corruptly.
John 5: 31-47
But I have testimony greater than John’s. The works that the Father gave me to accomplish, these works that I perform testify on my behalf that the Father has sent me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nazareth</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/19032020-thur3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/19032020-thur3/</guid>
      <description>Solemnity of Saint Joseph, spouse of the Blessed Virgin Mary2 Samuel 7:4-5A, 12-14A, 16Psalms 89:2-3, 4-5, 27 and 29Romans 4:13, 16-18, 22Matthew 1:16, 18-21, 24AThe feast days of the Virgin Mary moves us to contemplate the astonishing truth that lies at the heart of our faith: In Jesus, God has come to us in the flesh! Today’s Solemnity of Saint Joseph, Husband of the Virgin Mary, offers us another window into that truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bring us back to You</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/12032020-thur2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/12032020-thur2/</guid>
      <description>Thursday of the Second Week of Lent Year A, 2020Jeremiah 17:5-10Psalms 1:1-2, 3, 4, and 6Luke 16:19-31 The Lenten season is sometimes accompanied with barrenness and dryness and this dryness I speak of finds its way into our daily lives through our preoccupation with consuming more and more; our preoccupation with our wants; our preoccupation with what we do and with what others may think of us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help us to be eager in doing your will</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/05032020-thur1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/05032020-thur1/</guid>
      <description>Thursday of the First Week in Lent Year A 2020Esther C: 12, 14-16, 23-25Psalms 138:1-2AB, 2CDE-3, 7C-8Matthew 7:7-12We are in the first full week of Lent, and today’s readings tell us not to be shy in our prayer, but to sincerely ask, and beg God for what we need.
The prayer of Queen Esther in today’s first reading is a very simple powerful prayer of someone in mortal peril, especially the final petition of her prayer, &amp;ldquo;come to my help, for I am alone and have no one but you, Lord&amp;rdquo;, reminds us to pray for courage when we are afraid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love, Obey and Stay</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/27022020-thur0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/27022020-thur0/</guid>
      <description>Thursday after Ash Wednesday Year A 2020Deuteronomy 30: 15-20Luke 9: 22-25I certainly cannot remember the exact moment when the ashes got rubbed off my forehead yesterday. Not that I am bothered anyway – it was an outward sign pointing to an inward effect. It called us to repentance and conversion, while reminding us where we shall go after now.
By now the ashes must have left our foreheads too – sweat, wind, morning shower, or an overnight transfer onto our pillows.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>