<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tuesday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/tuesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tuesday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/tuesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Are we truly fulfilling God’s plan for our life?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/07042020-tue6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/07042020-tue6/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of Holy Week Year A 2020Isaiah 49:1-6Psalms 71:1-2, 3-4A, 5AB-6AB, 15 and 17John 13:21-33, 36-38While that question should be a key focus for each of us each and every day, is it really something we should contemplate during Holy Week? Yet today’s readings certainly seem to point us back to that fundamental issue.
In the first reading for today, we see a clear picture that God had a plan for Isaiah from the very beginning of his life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O Lord, hear my prayer, and let my cry come to you</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/31032020-tue5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/31032020-tue5/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Numbers 21:4-9Psalms 102:2-3, 16-18, 19-21John 8:21-30The words in the psalm today should be the words of our prayers during this global pandemic of COVID-19. Looking around the world, in some places some have lived weeks working from home, while some are experiencing restricted movements, lockdown and respecting the physical distancing expectations. In checking in with, friends, and family near and far, there is a mix of emotions – overwhelmed, relieved to be safe or secure in their jobs, sad to be missing friends and family, mourning the loss of loved ones, not to attend to as to issues promptly, not sure what tomorrow would be, cancellations of weddings, and other celebrations that will not be what was imagined, scared, anxious, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The healing at the pool of Bethesda</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/24032020-tue4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/24032020-tue4/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of the Fourth Week of Lent Year A 2020Ezekiel 47:1-9, 12Psalms 46:2-3, 5-6, 8-9John 5:1-16A miraculous, cleansing, life-giving river that stems from the temple as a trickle, becomes deeper and deeper, until it is a mighty torrent, would, indeed awe-inspiring. This would especially be true in the arid surroundings of the temple.
Our guide down this miraculous river seems to wade, float, and then swim with us until we, overwhelmed by the power and depth of the water, clamber onto a lush bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solemnity of Saint Patrick, Bishop, Missionary</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/17032020-tue3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/17032020-tue3/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of the Third Week of Lent Year A 2020Daniel 3:2.11-20.Psalm 25:4-5ab.6; 7cd. 8-9.Matthew 18:21-35.We venerate Patrick on this his feast day because he spent himself in proclaiming the gospel on this island, bringing Christ to huge numbers of people. He says of himself in his Confessions, &amp;ldquo;The love of Christ gave me to these people to serve them humbly and sincerely for my entire lifetime&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They do not practise what they preach</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/10032020-tue2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/10032020-tue2/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of the Second Week in Lent Year A 2020Isaiah 1:10, 16-20Psalms 50:8-9, 16bc-17, 21 and 23Matthew 23:1-12In the gospel reading Jesus contrasts the attitude of the religious leaders of his day who wanted and expected to receive various forms of honour with what should be the attitude of his own disciples, namely the readiness and willingness to serve others.
Jesus was not opposed to some form of leadership among his own followers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lord, open my lips, and my mouth shall declare your praise</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/03032020-tue1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/03032020-tue1/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday of the First Week of Lent Year A 2020Isaiah 55:10-11Psalms 34:4-5, 6-7, 16-17, 18-19Matthew 6:7-15I have come to better understand my relationship with God in terms of trust. Not only can God’s people trust in God but God wants to trust us.
The first reading in Isaiah today tells us that we can trust God’s word to be a fertile and fruitful seed that will achieve God’s ends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>