<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wednesday on Diamond of Dew</title>
    <link>https://example.com/categories/wednesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wednesday on Diamond of Dew</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/categories/wednesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The tragedy of betrayal</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/08042020-wed6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/08042020-wed6/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday of Holy Week Year A 2020Isaiah 50:4-9APsalms 69:8-10, 21-22, 31 and 33-34Matthew 26:14-25Holy Week, 2020, and a pandemic rages across the world. Go back 102 years to April, 1918 (Easter was on March 31 that year) and the inception of what would become the world-wide flu pandemic. An April public health document reported severe flu cases and several deaths, social distancing was not widespread, and deaths spiked significantly in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If the Son makes you free, you will be free indeed</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/01042020-wed5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/01042020-wed5/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday of the Fifth Week of Lent Year A 2020Daniel 3:14-20, 91-92, 95Daniel 3:52, 53, 54, 55, 56John 8:31-42Facing the truth is often painful but it can be liberating. What is sometimes put out as the truth is not always the full truth. One particular slant on an issue can easily be presented as the full truth. Full truth does not come our way easily; we have to keep on seeking the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am the Handmaid of the Lord</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/25032020-wed4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/25032020-wed4/</guid>
      <description>Solemnity of the Annunciation of the LordIsaiah 7:10-14; 8:10Psalms 40:7-8A, 8B-9, 10, 11Hebrews 10:4-10Luke 1:26-38Just when people think they have God figured out, that they know what God wants from them, God instead surprises them.
In the first reading, the Lord tells Ahaz to ask for a sign, but Ahaz, based on his preconceived ideas about how God operates, refuses. To do what God asks would violate what he believes God prefers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whoever obeys and teaches these commandments will be called greatest in the Kingdom of Heaven.</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/18032020-wed3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/18032020-wed3/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday of the Third Week of Lent Year A 2020Deuteronomy 4:1, 5-9Psalms 147:12-13, 15-16, 19-20Matthew 5:17-19As a Catholic, a parent/teacher, not an accomplished theologian, I find one of the most inspirational qualities of the Gospels of our faith to be their simplicity.
What I mean is that as the master teacher, Jesus does what we all strive to do as parents/teachers, which is to make complex and abstract concepts more accessible and understandable for the Children/students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Son of Man came not to be served but to serve</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/11032020-wed2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/11032020-wed2/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday of the Second Week of Lent Year AJeremiah 18:18-20Psalms 31:5-6, 14, 15-16Matthew 20:17-28We often find in the Jewish Scriptures that those who are in some dire situation address an agonizing question to God. One such example is to be found in today’s first reading. In response to those who are plotting his downfall, Jeremiah asks God, &amp;ldquo;Should evil be returned for good?&amp;quot; Although, in theory, we would answer ‘no’ to Jeremiah’s question, in practice we are all aware that evil is often returned for good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sign of Jonah for an Evil Generation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/04032020-wed1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/04032020-wed1/</guid>
      <description>Wednesday of the First Week in Lent Year A 2020 Jonah 3:1-10 Psalms 51:3-4, 12-13, 18-19 Luke 11:29-32When I see any reference to Jonah, I think of the story of the little girl who in Sunday school was mesmerized with the account of Jonah being swallowed by a whale and spending three days and nights in the whale’s belly. The next day in science class, she very excitedly recounts the story to her science teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fasting and Abstinence</title>
      <link>https://example.com/posts/26022020-wed0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/posts/26022020-wed0/</guid>
      <description>Ash Wednesday Year A 2020Joel 2: 12- 18 2 Cor. 5:20- 6:2Matthew 6:1-6, 16-18Today the whole church begins a very intense spiritual journey. It is a journey of repentance, a journey of renewal, a journey of conversion and a journey of healing. Whatever forms the journey may take, it is always a journey back into the heart of God. It is not just today but even for the whole season of Lent, that we are called to deepen our spiritual life with penance and repentance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>